[OVERDO]
[Episode 22]
-Great! -Great!
-Congratulations! -Congratulations!
What a perfect match.
They look so good together.
He is so handsome.
Miss Fang looks so beautiful in that wedding dress.
So beautiful.
The bride is also very beautiful.
Yes.
She looks amazing.
This wedding dress is so gorgeous.
Truly a match made in heaven.
Wait.
That is not Ren Susu.
My view is completely blocked.
It seems I'll just have to play it by ear.
Li Rongzhang.
I will never let you leave here today.
Boze.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
I'm envious of this lovely couple
That's getting married.
Why does he look like he's seen a ghost?
He made a huge scene at home a few days ago.
I guess he's still upset.
What is he up to again now?
Why do I have a bad feeling?
Dear guests,
Please quiet down for a moment.
Bride,
Do you take
This man standing before you as your husband,
To love him, respect him, and comfort him...
Ren Susu, what exactly are you planning to do?
Whether you're in good times or bad,
In sickness and in health,
To be faithful,
Never abandoning him,
Until
The end of your life?
I do.
I am willing to walk side by side with you,
Be your safe harbor,
Love you,
And I promise
To go through all the ups and downs with you for the rest of my life.
Groom,
Do you take
This woman standing before you as your wife,
To love her,
Care for her,
And respect her
As you cherish your own soul,
In sickness and in health,
To be faithful,
Never abandoning her,
Until
The end of your life?
I do.
I will always
Protect you.
I will always protect you, keeping you under my wing.
I will always love you.
I will be
Your most loyal partner.
And I also promise
That I will support your freedom
And dreams.
Ms. Ye...
I pronounce you husband and wife.
-Great! -Great!
Please be seated, everyone.
Good opportunity.
Qingyu! Qingyu!
Qingyu!
Mother! Mother!
Brother!
Qingyu...
Somebody!
Get the car ready!
Doctor! Where is the doctor?
Hurry!
Get the car and send him to the hospital!
Qingyu!
Qingyi,
You can't be willful anymore.
Boze,
Take good care of Qingyi.
The Murong family
Will always be your home.
Fang Mulan!
You bitch!
Qingyi!
Qingyu, don't fall asleep.
Qingyu, don't fall asleep, okay?
I'll get the doctor. I'll get the doctor...
Zhihong,
I once
Dreamed
Of this wedding.
I'm sorry.
You have nothing to be sorry for.
I can't fly... with you anymore.
Qingyu.
Principal!
I heard you are very impressive.
How about we race in the sky?
Principal.
She's a newcomer at our aviation school,
Ye Zhihong.
Let's race, then.
Qingyu.
Don't fall asleep.
Please don't fall asleep.
Qingyu, don't fall asleep.
Qingyu, please don't fall asleep. Qingyu...
Qingyu.
Why do you think
You will lose your dream if you are with me?
Why
Are you not even willing to give it a try?
Please don't fall asleep.
You...
You said you would stay with me.
Who ordered you to do this?
No one!
No one.
It's perfectly justified for me to avenge my father.
She is the one I want to kill!
Fang Mulan!
You bitch!
Three years ago,
You killed my father,
And now you destroyed my family.
It's justified for me
-to kill you a thousand times over! -Shut up!
Speak.
Who told you this?
You probably don't know—
She is not the daughter of the Fang family at all.
Her name is Ren Susu.
Our Huo family orphanage took her in,
Giving her a cheap life.
Ask your dear sister-in-law
If she dares to take off her veil
And show everyone—
Shut up!
I've thought it through.
We have no future together at all.
You are the eldest young master of the Murong family,
The famous young marshal of the Cheng Army.
And I am a helpless orphan girl.
Your wife
Should be someone
Who can share your family responsibilities with you.
But that's not what I want.
Congratulations.
Qingyu.
I should have been brave earlier.
Ms. Ye,
Leave quickly.
I will make arrangements for the rest.
I think
The principal's greatest wish
Is probably for you to be safe.
Zhihong.
I'll see you off here.
♪ I happened to ♪
Actually,
♪ Hear your name ♪
My place is in the other direction.
♪ And all the memories ♪
♪ Came flooding back ♪
I know.
♪ There I stood in the falling snow ♪
♪ Wrapped in my coat ♪
I know
You always take a detour to walk me—
♪ My heart pounding ♪
Pretending to bump into me.
♪ Walking down that old road ♪
♪ Stopping every few steps ♪
I can turn around,
♪ In the misty train car ♪
Qingyu.
♪ I wish I could ask you once more ♪
I can turn around.
♪ If you have any ♪
Zhihong,
♪ New corny jokes to tell ♪
I have to go.
♪ Memories are like falling into a trap ♪
♪ Full of mud ♪
Qingyu, don't go.
♪ The more I struggle, the more suffocated I become ♪
♪ But I couldn't resist collecting them ♪
♪ I keep collecting ♪
Qingyu...
♪ Every word and comment ♪
I really miss you.
♪ They speak of you ♪
♪ You're becoming clear ♪
♪ So far yet so clear ♪
♪ Ever since forgetting you ♪
♪ Became second nature ♪
Principal.
What did you write?
I wrote,
♪ I still can't erase ♪
"I hope Ms. Ye's paper airplane
♪ Completely erase ♪
Will fly the highest."
♪ The certainty of my hand in yours ♪
♪ You are so clear ♪
♪ So close and so clear ♪
♪ If you possibly still have the courage ♪
♪ Then take me away from here ♪
♪ Please stop doubting ♪
♪ My determination to run away with you ♪
[Funeral]
[Modern Surgery: General and Operative]
[To: Murong Qingyi]
[Three years ago, Nancheng, Murong Mansion]
Qingyi!
What brings you back?
You were injured, shouldn't I come back to visit you?
If you're always on crutches,
You will never recover.
I strained my ligament,
And need to rest.
Give me the crutches.
You've got some nerve!
Stop!
Run faster!
Give it to me!
Qingyu.
Are you okay?
I haven't fully recovered yet.
Seriously.
You learned some skills
And came back to mess with me.
When people are excited, adrenaline is released,
Which speeds up recovery.
I'm helping you.
Helping me?
Excited?
Adrenaline is released, huh?
How about I release it on you—
You can't hit me!
I've worn the watch
You gifted me for a long time.
If it breaks, I'll be heartbroken.
Sit down.
You're so glib now.
Are you back
Because something's wrong this time?
Nothing's wrong.
You were injured,
So I came back to see you.
You missed me?
By the way, Qingyu,
I've never told you
Why I study medicine, right?
To heal the wounded
And rescue the dying.
It's more than that.
When we were young, you told me
You wanted to learn to fly a plane.
I thought then,
When the plane flies high,
There must be a reliable doctor on the ground.
I wanted
To protect you
In my own way.
So sentimental.
Qingyi.
I know
You meant
What you said
About protecting me.
Besides being happy,
I was also thinking,
[To: Murong Qingyi]
Is being a doctor
What you truly want?
I thought about it
But couldn't find an answer.
But there's one thing
I can't say enough times
To you.
Qingyi,
I only want you
To do what you want,
Go where you want to go,
And live freely following your heart.
You disappear and run away from home at the drop of a hat!
Do you know there are people who are worried about you?
Who?
Me!
No matter how high you fly,
Look back—
I
Will be waiting for you to come home.
[Murong Residence]
[Funeral]
It's the 9th
In 4 days—
Suitable for marriage.
This is your own choice.
Actually, you could also choose...
To let others avenge me.
Since I promised not to involve the Murong family,
I wouldn't let my sisters take risks for me either.
If I had listened to your advice back then,
Would none of this have happened?
[Funeral]
[Mourning]
[Mourning couplet]
Young Master Li, the luggage is loaded.
The Li family has been waiting outside for 2 hours.
My surname isn't Li.
Let them wait if they want to.
What does it have to do with me?
When your mind is disturbed,
Your writing will be disturbed too.
You won't be able to write
The two characters "Murong" well.
Brother,
Must I go?
I don't want to leave.
[Mu]
Look at the character "Mu," it has 3 dots—
Just like 3 brothers with deep affection.
No matter how it is written,
The structure of these 3 dots
Will never change.
Brother.
Am I a child of the Murong family,
Or the Li family?
Boze.
No matter where you are
Or what you do in the future,
You are always a member of the Murong family.
The Murong family
Will always protect you.
As long as we are around,
We have a home.
Mother.
I wrote an elegy for Qingyu.
Your handwriting
Is exactly like your brother's.
Qingyu.
You are alone over there,
So cold and lonely.
How can we not worry about you?
Jinrui.
The things I asked you to prepare,
Are they ready?
Boze,
Come.
Come with me
To tidy up your brother's wardrobe.
Let's go.
If it weren't for this accident,
You would already be husband and wife.
Husband and wife should
Live
And die together—
Never to be separated.
Let me go!
I think
You also can't bear to leave him
So lonely over there, right?
Yes.
Someone must accompany you.
That way,
You won't be so lonely,
And won't become a wandering ghost.
Let me go!
What are you going to do?
Qingyu,
Don't be afraid.
She will come join you soon.
[Funeral]
Seal the coffin.
Why are you here?
You are not welcome here.
I'm here to see my brother for the last time.
Where is Sister-in-law?
Why are you always thinking about your sister-in-law?
Get out!
I'm keeping vigil for your brother!
Get out of the way!
Someone!
Throw him out!
You are absolutely insane!
Someone,
Take Miss Fang away.
Yes.
Cheng Jinzhi,
You are a lunatic!
How could you do such an evil thing?
She's a living person!
Don't think that just because your brother is dead,
You can reach the top in one step.
I'm telling you—
It is not your place
To decide things for the Murong family.
Why?
Why do I not have a say?
I was trying to warn the Murong family back then
When I was drugged with opium and lost my mind.
I risked my life for that information,
But you didn't believe me.
That's why Murong Feng
Was at the scene of the explosion.
You are the one who killed your husband,
Not me.
Shut up!
Why should I believe you?
You are just a dog raised by Li Rongzhang.
He could easily use you
To give false information.
You don't accept discipline,
Disrespect your parents,
And ignore admonishments.
And now you've brought death to my Qingyu.
Right.
Even if you didn't kill your father,
Qingyu died because of you!
Nonsense!
It's because of you.
You are the jinx of the Murong family.
You made our family become like this.
You are a jinx.
I don't have a son like you.
Cheng Jinzhi,
Because you love Murong Feng,
You forced him
To stay by your side forever.
But ask yourself,
Did Murong Feng love you?
Shut up!
How did you treat Qingyu?
You treated him like a puppet.
He never lived a second for himself in his whole life.
It's all because you want to manipulate everyone
That this family became like this!
Shut up! Shut up! Shut your trap!
Why wasn't it you who died?
Why wasn't it you?
I tell you,
I've long been disgusted
With everything about the Murong family.
The Murong family rules state:
♪ Must it take heartache ♪
Whoever wants to break ties with the family
♪ To know my heart belongs to you? ♪
Must suffer 3 stabs.
♪ Hearts cold no more ♪
♪ Is every sweet dream ♪
♪ Destined to fade away? ♪
I will give myself
The first stab today.
♪ Don't let it end in smoke ♪
I couldn't choose my birth.
♪ Never back down, hold my ground ♪
But at least I can
♪ Till I've given my all ♪
Choose how to live my life.
♪ We ♪
♪ Must be together ♪
♪ Forevermore ♪